Good morning.
Kyoko. Kyoko.
Miyamura-kun's here to
take you to school, Kyoko.
Good morning, Hori-san.
It was your idea to walk together.
You said we should leave early.
You were watching that horror special
into the wee hours of the morning.
Go get changed.
And wash your face, too.
Hey, Miyamura-kun, want some coffee?
Oh, thank you.
This is where the alleged murder took place.
Where did that happen?
Police are attempting to locate
the victim's younger brother,
A neighboring prefecture. How scary.
who may have information
pertinent to the case.
For our next story...
Now for today's weather.
Man, it's cold.
Most of the country will have clear skies,
and cold northerly winds
will largely be kept at bay.
Thank you for the food.
Northern Japan will see
unseasonably warm temperatures.
She hasn't come back...
She hasn't come back!
The east will see average
or above average temperatures.
Um, could I go knock on her door?
Western Japan, Okinawa, and the Amami
Islands will see normal temperatures.
Sure.
Wait, she hasn't come back yet?
Hori-san?
Hori-san, I'm coming in.
She fell back to sleep...
You're asleep! You're asleep! Wake up!
Are you going to go
without brushing your hair?
No.
In that case, get up and turn around.
Hori-san, Hori-san! We're gonna be late.
Gotta go to the bathroom...
Okay, I'll put on my shoes and wait for you.
See you!
Yeah. Have a good day.
M-Miyamura!
Styled
What happened to my hair?!
Well, it was a mess...
I look like I'm going to a party!
I didn't think I could get
the ponytail right.
Oh, man!
Are you gonna take it down?
It doesn't go with my uniform!
So you're gonna take it down?
D-Does it look good?
It's not about how good it looks. I don't really know how
to do hair, but I worked really hard to make it nice
anyway, so I don't want it to just go to waste.
Yeah.
Fine, I'll keep it like this.
Yay!
So it's okay? It's not weird, is it?
No, it's not weird.
It's really cute.
I'm cute?
I didn't know I was so good at buns.
Hori, you look so cute!
I want a bun, too!
Hey, lookin' good. Did you do that yourself?
Like it?
I might try one, too.
I'm not sure your hair is long enough.
What? It's not?
He's right.
Oh...
Kyon-Kyon, that's so cute!
What's the occasion?
Nothing special.
Did you have a change
of heart about something?
Her hair is probably too fine.
No, no, I just felt like it.
Hey, what are you staring at?
I figured it might be nice for a change.
Wh-What?
It's great! Are you gonna change your image?
President... you don't have enough.
I might not be ready for that.
It wouldn't work out.
Am I lacking in something?!
Oh, Kono-san...
Tied to the side
That might look better than a bun.
Everyone's different.
Thanks for waiting!
Everyone's been complimenting my hair.
Of course.
You look cute.
You're really the cutest of all.
BLUUUSH
Ouch!
Senseless violence!
You can do my hair again sometime.
Maybe I'll try a braid next time.
Does she like the bun?
Oh, can you handle that?
My neck feels cold.
Does it?
Pom
You'll ruin it!
What are they doing?
I can't stand how silky Miyamura's hair is.
It doesn't stick up funny,
and a comb passes right through it.
Is that so?
I'm just so jealous!
If it never sticks up funny, then make it.
So your solution is
"if there's no bread, just eat cake"?
I mean, if you tie hair up,
it kinda holds like that for a while, right?
It'd only be temporary,
but you could try that.
I get it!
That's easier than using a hair iron.
Don't go overboard, Kyo-chan...
Ting
All done!
What did I do to deserve this?
There.
That should do it.
Thank you, Sengoku-kun.
Oh, it was nothing.
I thought we were keeping things organized,
but I guess we had more
things than we thought.
We're constantly getting
more papers and stuff.
But I must say...
I was surprised to see you up on
a chair cleaning the top of the cabinets.
You could've gotten hurt.
But I wanted to dust up there.
You don't like dust?
Yoshikawa-kun and Iura-kun
have been coughing sometimes.
I thought it might be the dust.
Did I catch you in the middle
of talking about my awesomeness?
No, you didn't.
You did not.
No?!
Are you organizing stuff?
Yeah, since we won't be
using this room much longer.
Hey, this box looks like it might fall.
Oh, Sengoku-kun just put it...
I'll take it down for now.
Does this go on top of the cabinet, too?
Ah, th-thank you!
That's a big help—
I know Ishikawa-kun's gotten
strong by doing sports,
but what about you, Iura-kun?
Where did you get that extra muscle?
Maybe from helping my
grandpa move furniture.
Furniture?!
I took out the trash.
Welcome back, Remi—
Stare...
Hori-san?
Huh?
Ayasaki-san was throwing
things away in random bins.
Next time, separate the recyclables
before you give it to her.
Remi!
I'm sorry, Kyon-Kyon!
Thank you for helping her, Hori-san.
I don't think there will be
a next time, though.
I guess you're right.
Is Ayasaki-san around?
Oh, everyone's here.
What is it? Do you need me
for something, Yanagin?
N-No, I just found a cell phone
I recognized in the trash area.
I saw you put it down without looking
when we were throwing stuff away.
Oh!
Thanks, Yanagin!
It's nothing.
Are you organizing in here?
I can help.
Yanagi-kun, this stuff is pretty heavy—
Someone might trip on this,
so I'll move it over to the corner.
Miyamura-kun, I need you here!
What's with him?
He wants someone weaker than him here
to make him feel better.
What a small man.
You called?
Whoa, he's carrying something
that looks heavy!
Miyamura-kun, what is that?
What're you doing with it?
Yasuda told me to take it.
He's giving back everything he's
confiscated during the school year.
Oh, like magazines and stuff.
Yasuda couldn't carry it himself.
Me & Yasuda (?) ← Yanagi-kun ← Miyamura-kun ← Iura-kun ← Ishikawa-kun
Muscle & Strength Ranking (Tentative)
Depressed
Well, there's not that big
a difference between us all.
Oh?
Me & Yasuda (?) ← Yanagi-kun ← Miyamura-kun ← Iura-kun ← Ishikawa-kun ← Kyo-chan (Hall of Fame)
The hall-of-famer is saying something.
What?
Sengoku-kun is fine the way he is!
I'll get stronger for him!
You're amazing, Remi.
R-Remi, I appreciate it,
but I like you the way you are, too.
Hey...
Yasuda made me bring this here.
Is Yasuda even weaker than Yoshikawa?!
Yoshikawa-san, I'll take that!
Thanks, Yanagi-kun.
This is quite heavy.
Yanagi-kun, be careful!
Chagrin...
Are you okay?
Muscle & Strength Ranking
Miyamura-kun & Yanagi-kun
↓
Yoshikawa-san
Me & Yasuda
(Confirmed)
Now I feel sorry for him.
Hey, the heavy stuff is all on one side.
That'd make it hard to carry.
I'd probably drop it, too.
Thanks, guys...
There's a postcard in here.
It was probably stuck in a magazine.
Maybe this one.
Hey, grab that pile.
Oh, I haven't seen this in forever!
Miyamura, once we're done...
Yeah.
What's wrong, Iura?
Sengoku, don't start reading it!
But doesn't it take you back?
I think...
I want to go to the beach.
That's right! We were talking about going.
Indeed! Someone can get
a license and drive us.
In a car? Awesome!
Our troop will have fun
no matter where we go!
Graduation
Don't call us a troop.
Are we ants?
Iura-kun, how about "group" instead?
Yeah, hey, hey! That's it, Akane!
Karaoke
I know, right?
Wanna check out that shop
we saw in the magazine?
Wait, for real?
Yeah!
Let's go!
Sota, what do you want to eat today?
A rice omelet!
What, again?
Yep, again!
I wonder if we still have ketchup...
Kyo-chan.
Mathematics II
Thanks.
You're finally giving it back!
You said you wouldn't have math today.
You're supposed to give it back
right after class ends.
Um...
Sengoku-kun was helping
the teacher after class.
Oh, I see.
That makes sense.
See you.
Yeah.
Oh, Hori!
Are you free after school?
Um...
Hori likes to go straight home after school.
Right?
Yeah, sorry.
Oh, okay. No worries.
Some of us are getting together to hang out,
so I was wondering if you wanted in.
That's all.
Looks like it's just us!
Toru really likes you, y'know?
Oh, come on. He just invited me to hang out.
Yeah, but how many times does that make?
You get invited out all the time.
I'm just there to increase the headcount.
What?
It's so windy!
That scared me!
Maybe I'll close the window.
Yeah.
The next thing I knew,
she was wearing the same shoes.
The heck?! That's how she's
trying to get friendly with you?
I just pretended not to notice.
That's what I'd do.
And then...
Oh, sorry.
No, I was...
And then, even with the same shoes,
she starts a fight with me.
Huh? Why?
Get this... It was about takoyaki.
Huh?!
Sorry we ran into you.
No, it's okay. Thank you.
Are you on the student council?
Yeah.
Must be a lot of work.
It's nothing but odd jobs.
There's someone on the roof.
I bet it's nice up there.
Not that I have any business going.
It's so cold!
Hurry up!
Wow...
That guy has no intention
of participating whatsoever.
Hori!
Yeah.
Student Council
Here.
Skull Ninja
Konoha
Thank you!
Sengoku said you'd have a copy.
There are more in the student council room.
Help yourself anytime.
Manga isn't allowed in school, so
the student council shouldn't have any!
But I'll still borrow it.
It'll be our secret.
Oh, Hori-san.
What are you guys up to?
I'm borrowing a book from Kono-san.
It's manga, though.
Really? You can come today?
Yep.
Great! I'll invite Shu, too.
Mama's coming home early today.
I'm gonna sing my heart out!
Just don't hog the mic.
What's wrong, Kyo-chan?
Karaoke...
You're coming, right, Sakura?
I get the feeling that we're missing someone.
Maybe just to listen.
But you sing anime songs while
cleaning the council room.
Oh.
How do you know that?!
Yanagi!
We got to be friends in our elective class.
Thank you for having me.
If he's bothering you, just tell us.
Yeah, spill it.
How would I be bothering him?
H-He's not bothering me at all!
Bye-bye.
See you tomorrow.
Crap, my phone...
Um, what's his name?
Never mind. I'll get it myself.
Here.
Th-Thank you.
We found each other
Hey, Miyamura...
Hmm?
What is it, Hori-san?
Nothing.
Sorry, I was daydreaming.
Are you okay?
What's got you so spaced out?
All of...
All of the coincidences that had to
happen to make this moment possible.
If even one hadn't happen, the world
might be completely different.
If that's true...
Maybe it was destiny
that brought us together like this.
Maybe.
I bet that no matter what we'd done,
we would have found each other.
Katagiri High School 63rd Graduation Ceremony
Every day was new and different.
I won't pretend I remember all of it.
Most of the memories have
faded and vanished,
but many are just as vivid
as the day they happened.
Katagiri High School 63rd Graduation Ceremony
I'm sure they're always going to be.
And starting now...
Miyamura.
We're going out for sushi today. Wanna come?
Yeah!
Okay! Let's go!
Kyosuke will be glad to have you.
He'll be obnoxious, of course.
Great!
We're closer than before.
We used to be so shy we couldn't
look each other in the eye.
But now we can laugh together
and touch, even
without a particular reason.
I don't really know what
we're thinking when we do.
Even now, I'm still not sure.
Saying "life" feels a little overblown.
You might laugh at that.
But if we can walk the path ahead together,
I think that would be so wonderful.
When you look down at your own shadow,
don't forget that I'm by your side.
Don't forget that there's
a light shining on you.
And when I hang my head,
I'd like you to remind me
that I'm not alone.
Tell me.
Hey, Miyamura.
The sky looks so blue today.
It feels like we could go wherever we want.
I've never known the world like this.
I never knew there was
something so steadfast inside me.
Come on, Miyamura!
Look how pretty the cherry
blossoms are, Miyamura.
There's a gentle breeze.
Thank you for helping me see so much.
I'm overjoyed.
The words to describe it would be
so ephemeral they might just fly away.
So, just like the petals falling around us,
I want to take my time letting you know.
Journey
Katagiri High School
Miyamura?
Oh, sorry. Were you asleep?
No, I'm awake.
It's okay.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm not sure I get why,
but I just need to come, right?
Okay.
Shortcake, Mont Blanc crêpes,
cheesecake, choux cream...
Okay, I'm ready!
Fell back asleep!!
4 hours late
Hey, it's my bro!
H-H-H-H-Hori-san?
She was saying you're really late.
Oh, is that all?
We had our graduation ceremony yesterday,
so we were gonna take it easy today.
I brought some cakes. Want one?
Cake?
Do you have chocolate?
Oops... No, sorry.
You're here, Miyamura.
JOLT
Y-Yes! Sorry for being late.
I, uh, brought cake!
Maybe we can all have some...
Silence
Is she angry?
Okay.
Great. I'll go get some plates.
I'll bring the cakes.
Hori-san?
I've never done this before.
What?
Hey, can I have the strawberry one?
Oh, sure. Whichever you like.
Wh-What do you think?
She gave up the girly style!
It looks great!
L-Liar! You hesitated!
I mean it! It looks really great on you!
They didn't understand what I asked for!
About this long
I didn't think they'd cut it this short!
Easy, easy...
You look cute with short hair.
I wanted you to be the first person
to see it. That's why I called you.
I look like a boy.
Are you sure you don't mind?
I was thinking of getting a haircut, too.
Liar.
No, it's true.
Dad, we got cake!
Oh, it's Kyosuke. Welcome home.
Yeah...
What gives? Are you breaking up?
Where'd that come from?
Miyamura-kun, did something happen?
I went to the salon where
Hori-san usually goes.
So it's no big deal?
She wanted to normalize our hair lengths.
Gals and guys can have their hair
however long they want.
She gets hung up on the weirdest stuff.
What was that?
She paid to have it done.
Oh?
Kyoko-chan, your dad
might need a haircut, too.
Okay, then cut it.
So cold!
I've never had my hair this short
before, so it's kinda funny.
Feels awkward, does it?
A little...
When I'm with Hori-san, I get to
have all sorts of new experiences.
It's great that you and Kyoko match.
Maybe I really should get a haircut.
Should I cut it for you?
Maybe not.
Hori-san!